[
    {
        "question": "which among the Disciples of Jesus Christ said this, now the end of the Commandment is charity out of a pure heart and of a good conscience, and of faith unfeigned?",
        "answers": "John the Baptist, John the beloved, Paul",
        "correct_answer": "Paul",
        "book_of_bible": "1st timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "which is correct among these in the scripture above for there is one God, and one Mediator between God and men, which is the man -------?",
        "answers": "Moses, Peter, Christ Jesus",
        "correct_answer": "Christ Jesus",
        "book_of_bible": "1st timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "complete the given scripture with the correct_answer this is a true saying, if a man desire the office of a bishop he desired a good?",
        "answers": "life, work, home",
        "correct_answer": "work",
        "book_of_bible": "1 timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "which of these speaks expressively that in the latter times some shall depart from the faith?",
        "answers": "man, church, spirit",
        "correct_answer": "spirit",
        "book_of_bible": "1st timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "which verse of the bible talks about teaching otherwise and not consenting to wholesome words?",
        "answers": "1 timothy 6: 3, 1timothy 6: 1, 1 timothy 6: 6",
        "correct_answer": "1 timothy 6:3",
        "book_of_bible": "1 timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "which verse of the bible, \u2018was this scripture quoted, \u2019but Godliness with contentment is great gain?",
        "answers": "1 kings 6:6, 1 samuel6v:6, 1 timothy6:6",
        "correct_answer": "1 timothy 6:6",
        "book_of_bible": "1 timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "who is this scripture referring to \u2018not given to wine, no striker, not greedy of filthy lucre; but patient, not a brawler, not covetous?",
        "answers": "priest, bishop, husband",
        "correct_answer": "bishop",
        "book_of_bible": "1 timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "which of the following option is correct according to this scripture \u2018Unto --------- my own son in the faith; grace, mercy, and peace, from God our father and Jesus Christ our lord?",
        "answers": "Matthew, Paul, timothy",
        "correct_answer": "timothy",
        "book_of_bible": "1 timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "complete this verse in the bible, let the woman learn in silence with all--------?",
        "answers": "sincerity, passion, subjection",
        "correct_answer": "subjection",
        "book_of_bible": "1 timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "which of the disciples made this statement, now unto the king eternal, immortal, invisible, the only wise God, be honour and glory for ever and ever amen?",
        "answers": "john the Baptist, Paul, Matthew",
        "correct_answer": "Paul",
        "book_of_bible": "1 timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "who in the bible made this statement and about who but, when he was in Rome, he sought me out very diligently and found me?",
        "answers": "Paul and about Caesar, Paul about Aristarchus, Paul about Onesiphorus",
        "correct_answer": "Paul about Onesiphorus",
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "fill in this with the correct_answer of the disciple name only Luke is with me take -----and bring him with thee; for he is profitable to me for the ministry?",
        "answers": "Paul, Matthew, Mark",
        "correct_answer": "Mark",
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "which is the name of timothy mother and grandmother?",
        "answers": "Aquila and Priscilla, Lois and Eunice, Lois and Elizabeth",
        "correct_answer": "Lois and Eunice",
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy"
    },
    {
        "question": "when I call to remembrance the unfeigned faith that is in thee, which dwelt first in thy grandmother Lois and thy mother Eunice; and I am persuaded that in thee also?",
        "Who": "made this statement and to who",
        "answers": "Paul to timothy, Paul to Barnabas, Paul to john the Baptist",
        "correct_answer": "Paul to timothy"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy",
        "question": "which of this verse is true?",
        "answers": "the husbandman that laboureth must be first partaker of the fruits, the husbandman that laboureth must be the first partaker of the food, the husbandman that laboureth must be the first partaker of the meat.",
        "correct_answer": "the husbandman that laboureth must be the first partaker of the fruits"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy",
        "question": "which chapter of the bible was this quoted\u201d Study to show thyself approved unto God, a workman that needeth not to be ashamed, rightly dividing the word of truth?",
        "answers": "2nd timothy 2: 5,2nd timothy 2: 10,2nd timothy 2: 15",
        "correct_answer": "2nd timothy 2:15"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy",
        "question": "which book of the bible recorded this \u201cThis know also, that in the last days perilous times shall come?",
        "answers": "2nd timothy 3: 1, 2nd timothy 6: 1, 2nd timothy9:1",
        "correct_answer": "2nd timothy3: 1"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy",
        "question": "which book of the bible recorded this I have fought a good fight, I have finished my course, I have kept the faith?",
        "answers": "2nd timothy 4: 6, 2nd timothy 4: 7, 2nd timothy 4: 8",
        "correct_answer": "2nd timothy 4: 7"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy",
        "question": "fill in the correct_answer------- the coppersmith did me much evil; the lord reward him according to his works?",
        "answers": "Erastus, Gaius, alexander",
        "correct_answer": "alexander"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy",
        "question": "which of the disciples made this statement For I am now ready to be offered, and the time of my departure is at hand?",
        "answers": "Peter, John the Baptist, Paul",
        "correct_answer": "Paul"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd timothy",
        "question": "which of   these women in reference to the church in Asia was apostle Paul referring to?",
        "answers": "Lois and Eunice, Joanna and Susannah, Aquila and Priscilla",
        "correct_answer": "Aquila and Priscilla"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1 Corinthians",
        "question": "what does these actually mean, now concerning spiritual gifts, brethren I would not have you ignorant?",
        "answers": "in the dark, without understanding, lonely",
        "correct_answer": "without understanding"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which is the names of the disciples that Paul baptized?",
        "answers": "John the Baptist and john the beloved, Aristarchus and oneisphorus, Crispus and Gaius",
        "correct_answer": "Crispus and Gaius"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which book of the bible said this, for it is written, I will destroy the wisdom of the wise, and will bring to nothing the understanding of the prudent?",
        "answers": "1st Corinthians 1vs 6, 1st Corinthians 1vs 8, 1st Corinthians 1vs 19",
        "correct_answer": "1st corinthians1vs 19"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which among the disciples made this statement And I was with you in weakness, and in fear, and in much trembling?",
        "answers": "Peter, James, Paul",
        "correct_answer": "Paul"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which book of the bible is this found that your faith should not stand in the wisdom of men, but in the power of God?",
        "answers": "1st Corinthians 2vs 4, 1st peter2vs 4, 1st corinthians2vs 5",
        "correct_answer": "1st Corinthians 2vs 5"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "according to 1 Corinthians 3vs16, where does Paul imply that the temple of God was located?",
        "answers": "in the little town of Bethlehem, in heaven itself, within the physical bodies of believers",
        "correct_answer": "within the physical bodies of believers"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which of the gifts of the holy spirit did Paul imply in 1 Corinthians 14: 1,was superior to the rest?",
        "answers": "the ability to prophesy, speaking in tongues, applying the gift of knowledge",
        "correct_answer": "the ability to prophesy"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "who or what did Paul say could not inherit the kingdom of God in 1 Corinthians 15:50",
        "answers": "Animal, Angels, flesh and blood",
        "correct_answer": "flesh and blood"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which of this event is correct according to the book of the bible, Paul scolded the member of the church at Corinth for their flippant attitude concerning what church observance?",
        "answers": "partaking of the Lord\u2019s Supper, ordination of bishop and deacon, sharing of prayer blankets",
        "correct_answer": "partaking of the lord supper"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which of this gift did Paul mentioned that were available to the church?",
        "answers": "Joy, Peace, Word of knowledge",
        "correct_answer": "Word of knowledge"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Corinthians",
        "question": "which book of the bible was this recorded Therefore if any man be in Christ, he is  a new creature, old things are passed away; behold, all things are become?",
        "answers": "2 Corinthians 7vs 8, 2 Corinthians 5vs 17, 2 Corinthians5vs 17",
        "correct_answer": "2 Corinthians 5vs17"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "which of the following best expresses the view that most scholars hold about 2 Corinthians?",
        "answers": "it should be included in the Old Testament, it contains messages in secret code, it is composed of fragments from more than one letter",
        "correct_answer": "it is composed of fragments from more than one letter"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "with whom according to chapter6,should the Corinthians avoid being yoked?",
        "answers": "Romans collaborators, devils, unbelievers",
        "correct_answer": "unbelievers"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "which of these were Paul reason for not visiting the church at Corinth",
        "answers": "he was sick, he was in prison, he was at Rome",
        "correct_answer": "he was in prison"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "which chapter of the book of the bible was this recorded For our light affliction, which is but a moment, worketh for us a far more exceeding and eternal weight of glory?",
        "answers": "2 Corinthians 4vs 15, 2 Corinthians 4vs 16, 2 Corinthians 4vs 17",
        "correct_answer": "2 Corinthians 4vs 17"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "which chapter of the bible talks about not receiving the grace of God in vain?",
        "answers": "2 Corinthians 6vs 1, 2 Corinthians 6vs 2, 2 Corinthians 6vs 3",
        "correct_answer": "2 Corinthians 6vs1"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "which one of the disciples was speaking in this scripture \u201cO ye Corinthians, our mouth is open unto you, our heart is enlarged?",
        "answers": "John the Baptist, Peter, Apostle Paul",
        "correct_answer": "Apostle Paul"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "which verse of the bible was this recorded, \u201cBut this I say, he which Sows sparingly shall reap also sparingly; and he which Sows bountifully shall reap also bountifully?",
        "answers": "2 Corinthians 9vs 4, 2 Corinthians 9vs5, 2 Corinthians 9vs 6",
        "correct_answer": "2 Corinthians 9vs 6"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "complete the following chapter of the bible, Thanks be unto God for his unspeakable ----?",
        "answers": "love, grace, gift",
        "correct_answer": "gift"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "complete the following scripture of the bible; But he that  glorieth, let him glory in the ----?",
        "answers": "Men, Lord, Grace",
        "correct_answer": "Lord"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "2nd Corinthians",
        "question": "which names of disciples were mentioned in respect to the church in Thessalonians",
        "answers": "Paul ,Silvanus , Timotheus,  Gaius, Onesiphorus, Aristarchus, Peter, John, Luke",
        "correct_answer": "Paul Silvanus  Timotheus"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "question": "according to the scripture, Paul is writing to the Christian community in Thessalonica, of which roman province was Thessalonica the province?",
        "answers": "Asia, Achaea, Macedonia",
        "correct_answer": "Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "question": "what is the first word in the King James Version of 1 Thessalonians?",
        "answers": "Timotheus   Paul   Silvanus",
        "correct_answer": "Paul"
    },
    {
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "questions:": "According to Apostle Paul during his visits to Thessalonica he was with two others",
        "Which": "are ------ and ------",
        "answers": "Silvanus and Timotheus , Gaius and timothy ,Silas and timothy"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Silas and timothy",
        "book_of_bible": "1st   Thessalonians",
        "question": "According to the book of the bible in I Thessalonians   apostle Paul wrote some letters ,where was apostle Paul when he wrote these letters?",
        "answers": "Macedonia, Rome, Corinth"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Corinth",
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "question": "who did   Paul   said   was raised from the dead?",
        "answers": "Lazarus,  Jesus, peter"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Jesus",
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "question": "According to 1 thessalonians2:5 who does Paul say is their witness?",
        "answers": "Jesus, Angels, God"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "God",
        "book_of_bible": "1st   Thessalonians",
        "question": "According to 1 Thessalonians 2:2, where had Paul been giving rough treatment and grossly insulted",
        "answers": "Macedonia, Corinth, Phillipi"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Phillipi",
        "book_of_bible": "1st   Thessalonians",
        "question": "who did   Paul said   hindered them from going to Thessalonica sooner",
        "answers": "God, Satan,   angels"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Satan",
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "question": "According to   1 Thessalonica 2:17   who or what has prevented Paul from returning to visit the Thessalonians??",
        "answers": "man,   Satan,   God"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Satan",
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "question": "According to 1 Thessalonians 3:1-2 whom did Paul send back to Thessalonica?",
        "answers": "Silas timothy Silvanus"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Timothy",
        "book_of_bible": "1st Thessalonians",
        "question": "how man chapters is in the Book of Isaiah?",
        "answers": "66, 44, 24"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "66",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "According Isaiah1:2 hear oh heavens and give___",
        "answers": "Eyes, Supplication, Ear"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Ear",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "which cities where mentioned in the book of Isaiah?",
        "answers": "Sodom & Gomorrah, Sodom & Rome, Egypt & Gomorrah"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Sodom & Gomorrah",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "According Isaiah 60:8 who are these that fly as a ___ and as the ___ to their windows?",
        "answers": "Doves & Bird, Cloud & Winds, Cloud & Doves"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Cloud & Doves",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "who is the father of Isaiah?",
        "answers": "Amoz, Aaron, Amos"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Amoz",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "Isaiah 2:6 says \u201co house of Jacob, come ye and let us walk in the ____ of the Lord?",
        "answers": "Light, Grace, Speed"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Light",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "Isaiah 60 has how many verses?",
        "answers": "23, 22, 30"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "22",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "Isaiah 60:1 says Arise, shine for thy____ is come and the ____of the Lord is risen upon thee?",
        "answers": "Light & Glory, Light & Cloud, Blessing & Peace"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Light & Glory",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "Isaiah 60:22 says A little on shall become a _____ and a small one a ________ nation?",
        "answers": "Thousand and Strong, Hundred and soft, Million and Rough"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Thousand and Strong",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "which book is after the book of Isaiah?",
        "answers": "Ezekiel, Jeremiah, Lamentation"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Jeremiah",
        "book_of_bible": "Isaiah",
        "question": "how many chapters has the book of Jeremiah?",
        "answers": "52, 33, 100"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "52",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "who is the father of Jeremiah?",
        "answers": "Aaron, Hilkiah, Judah"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Hilkiah",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "Jehoiakim is the son of ___?",
        "answers": "Josiah, Isaiah, Zedekiah"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Josiah",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "who is the son of Josiah?",
        "answers": "Zedekiah, Zachariah, Zephaniah"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Zedekiah",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "According to Jeremiah 4:15 says\u201d for a voice declare from ___ and publish affliction from mount Ephraim?",
        "answers": "Gad, Dan, Israel"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Dan",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "Jeremiah 4:27 says\u201d for thus hath the Lord said, the whole land shall be ____;yet will I not make a full end",
        "answers": "Black, Waste, Desolate"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Desolate",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "___ book comes before Jeremiah?",
        "answers": "Isaiah, Esther, Obadiah"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Isaiah",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "____ book come after Jeremiah?",
        "answers": "Lamentation, Isaiah, Revelations"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Lamentation",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "according to Jeremiah 10:17\u201d gather up thy ___ out of the land, O inhabitant of the fortress?",
        "answers": "Wares, Loins, Space"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Wares",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "Jeremiah chapter 40, has how many verses?",
        "answers": "20, 30, 16"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "16",
        "book_of_bible": "Jeremiah",
        "question": "___ had a vision in Obadiah 1:1?",
        "answers": "Obadiah, Amos, Aaron"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Obadiah",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "in Obadiah 1:1 the Lord talk about ____?",
        "answers": "Edom, Eden, Ephraim"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Edom",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "According to Obadiah 1:1 an ____ was sent among the heathen..?",
        "answers": "Ape, Ambassador, Apple"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Ambassador",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "Obadiah has how many verses in total?",
        "answers": "21, 20, 22"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "21",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "Obadiah has how many chapters in total?",
        "answers": "1, 44, 9"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "according to Obadiah 1:20\u201dand the _____ of the captivity of this host of the children of Israel shall possess that of the ____?",
        "answers": "Canaanites, Ephraim, Gilead"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Canaanites",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "according to Obadiah 1:21\u201d and saviors shall come up on mount ___ to judge the mount of Esau and the kingdom shall be the Lords\u201d?",
        "answers": "Sinai, Zion, Esau"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Zion",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "Behold I have made thee small among the ___ thou art greatly despised?",
        "answers": "heathen, hidden, Eaten"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "heathen",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "Obadiah 1:17\u201dbut upon mount Zion shall be deliverance, and there shall be ___...?",
        "answers": "Grace, Peace, Holiness"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Holiness",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "According to Obadiah 1:18\u201d and the house of Jacob shall be a___ and the house of Joseph a _?",
        "answers": "Fire & Flame, Flame & Oil, Fire & Water"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Fire & Flame",
        "book_of_bible": "Obadiah",
        "question": "The book of Joel has how many chapters??",
        "answers": "1, 2, 3"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "Joel is the son of ___ ?",
        "answers": "Petheul, Peniel, Paul"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Petheul",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "The book of Joel has how many chapters in total ??",
        "answers": "70, 73, 76"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "73",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "The word of _____ came to Joel,according to joel 1:1?",
        "answers": "The Lord, The angels, Petheul"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "The  lord",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "Awake ye drunkards, and weep and howl, all ye drinkers of wine, because of  the new wine; for it is cut off from your __?",
        "answers": "mouth, skin, wine"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "mouth",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "Joel 3:1 says for behold, in those days, and in that time, when I shall bring again the captivity of ___ and Jerusalem",
        "answers": "Etophia, Judah, Cyprus"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Judah",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "the sun and the moon shall be___ and the stars withdraw their___?",
        "answers": "Darkened & Shinning, Darkened & Brightness, Darkened & Glory"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Darkened & Shinning",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "how many verses has the last chapter of Joel?",
        "answers": "22, 21, 20"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "21",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "Joel 2:15 says blow the ___ in Zion\u2026.?",
        "answers": "Trumpet, horn, sound"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Trumpet",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "Joel 3:20 says\u201d But Judah shall dwell forever, and Jerusalem from generation to__?",
        "answers": "Generation, Ever, Seeds"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Generation",
        "book_of_bible": "Joel",
        "question": "how many chapters has the book of Lamentation?",
        "answers": "5, 6, 7"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "5",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "Judah is gone into captivity because of ____?",
        "answers": "Affliction, Sin, Stubbornness"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Affliction",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "According to Lamentation 1:4 Zion mourn because none come to the solemn____?",
        "answers": "Break, Feasts, Wash"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Feasts",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "Lamentation 3:8 says Also when I cry and shout, he shutteth out my ____?",
        "answers": "Self, Prayer, Peace"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Prayer",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "I am the man that hath seen affliction by the rod of his____?",
        "answers": "Wrath, Mercy, face"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Wrath",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "which book is before Lamentation?",
        "answers": "Jeremiah, Job, Hosea"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Jeremiah",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "which book is after Lamentation?",
        "answers": "Ezekiel, Jeremiah, Job"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Ezekiel",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "Lamentation 5:2 says our inheritance is turned to ___ our houses ____?",
        "answers": "Strangers & Aliens, Aliens & Space, Strangers & Space"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Strangers & Aliens",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "According to Lamentation 5:17 for this our heart is faint, for this things our eyes are ____?",
        "answers": "Dim, Low, Doll"
    },
    {
        "correct_answer": "Dim",
        "book_of_bible": "Lamentation",
        "question": "Lamentation 5:19 says thou O Lord, remainest forever, thy throne from generation to ___?",
        "answers": "Eternity, Generation, Everlasting"
    }
]